Guide to the United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI. Office of the General Counsel
  - Subseries VI.4: Executive Office. Subject File
    - Loew's Agreement for Film (Box GC/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Loew's International Corp. Contract re Distribution of UNRRA Reports to the Americas (Box GC/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Luzon Stevedoring Co. (65) Part I (Box GC/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Luzon Stevedoring Co. (65) Part II (Box GC/13, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement and Contracts (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Mayronne Lumber and Supply Col (388), Marrero, L.A. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Mexican Glass Tubing Plant for Yugoslavia (234) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Mexican Supply Drive (27) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Mid-Hudson Warehouse Inc. (113) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Midway Packing Co. (68) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Monel Corp. (118) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Monmouttf Electric Co. (117) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Moore-McCormack Lines Inc. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Morelli Brothers (107) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - National Cold Storage Col New York (incl. Brooklyn) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - National Committee for Collection of Relief Supplies in Mexico (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Newfoundland Herring Rates (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - N.Y. Central Railroad Co. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Northwest Airlines Inc. (433) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Norwegian Fish Agreement (15) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Nurse Teacher Training Program (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Nurse Training Program (162) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - OFRRO Stockpile (74) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - OFLC/UNRRA (Office of Foreign Liquidation Commission) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - OFLC, UNRRA Claims against (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - OFLC Contract (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Omaha Horse & Mule Commission Co. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Owen Brothers (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Pacific Overseas Airlines Corp. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Perry Warehousing & Terminal Co. (5) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Public Building Administration (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Raymond J. Sabo Contract (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Refugee Relief Committee (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Retail Credit Co. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Robert Shaw US Bonded & Free Warehouses (112) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Ross Brothers Horse & Mule Co. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Sheep & Pigs Contract (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Ship Diversion (126) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Spain Exporters Association (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Stetson-Lainberton (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Straping Machine Contract (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Sub-committee on DPs (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Superintendent Co. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Terminal Stockyards (400) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Texaco (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Tidewater Stevedoring Corp. (235) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Transfer of Supplies and Equipment to UN (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Transfer of UNRRA library to UN (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Transportation Claims (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - TWA Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNESCO (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNESCO (73) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNESCO Preparatory Commission (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Unitarian Congregational Committees (136) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Unitarian Service Committee (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Unitarian Service Committee (101) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Unitarian Service Committee Czech Teaching Mission (175) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Unitarian Service Committee & The Congregation Christian Service Commission (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - United Express Lines Inc. (114) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - United National Clothing Collection (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UN - DPI (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Monetary & Financial Conference (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Payments to History, Archives and Records Personnel Transferred to UN (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA/FAO (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA/IRO (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA/UN Administrative Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA/UN Agreement Transfer of Certain Activities to UN (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Refugee Committee (138) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Information Office (134) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA-UN (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA-UNICEF (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA-UN, of UNRRA History (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Marine Claims, Assignment of (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Assignment for Claims (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - U.S. Freight Group A #1, Assignment of Claims (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, General Average Group A #2 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, Breach of Contract Group A #3 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, Sterling Freight Group A #4 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, U.S. Installment Account Group A #5 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, Freedman Account Group A #76 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, Glynne Roberts & Freedman Group B #1 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, Open Accounts of Employees & Other Assignment of Group B #2 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, Argentine Tax Group B #3 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims, General Group B #6 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Uruguayan Linseed Oil Universal Grain Group (157) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - US Maritime Commission Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Vendors Consolidating Co. Inc. (100) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Veteran Air Express Co. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Voluntary Agency (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Voluntary Agency (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Voluntary Agency (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - American Christian Committee for Refugees (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - American Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - American Zone (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Canadian Allied Relief (First Collection) (1) (See File #37 for 2nd Canadian Collection) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Canadian Divisional Relief (137) (See File #1 for 1st Canadian Collection) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Greek War Relief(II) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Jewish Committees for Relief Abroad (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - United Nations Clothing Contract (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Agreement with Voluntary Agencies (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - British Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - British Zone (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreements (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Church World Service (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Don Guisse (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - French Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - French Zone (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Friends Relief Service (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Girl Scouts of the US. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Greek Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - H.I.A.S. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - IGCR (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - International Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - ICRS (international Committee of the Red Cross) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Italian Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - JCRA (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - JAFP (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Mennonite Central Committee (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - NCWC (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - ORT (Box GC/14, Folder Side 1)
    - Netherlands Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Polish Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - London (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Refugee Relief Committee (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Unitarian Service Committee (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - US Committee for Care for European (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Vaad Hatzala (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Association of Girl Guides & Girl Scouts (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Council of Churches (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Jewish Congress (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Student Relief (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - YMCA (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Yugoslav Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - AJDC (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - APWR (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Belgian Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - WSA Waiver (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - W (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Waiver Agreements in Connection: SS Newton D. Barker, John H. Murphy, James McHenry, Julien Poydras, Moses Roaers ect. Marine Claims (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - WSA/UN Waiver (Supplement) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Waiver of Claims (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Waiver of Claims, Shipping (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - War Shipping Administration (13) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - War Shipping Administration, Waiver of Claims (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Waiver of Navy Salvage Claims (57) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Washington Electric Cooler Co. (435) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Waterman Airlines Inc. (320) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Water Airlines Inc. Contracts (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - International Wheat (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - WHO-ICEF-UNESCO (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - WHO Original Signed Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Working Fund (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Festivals for Friendships Inc. (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Today Inc. (415) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - World Today Inc. Contract (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - W.R. Grace Co. (23) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreements with Member Governments (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - H.I.A.S.ter Agreements with Member Government (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
  - Subseries VI.5: Executive Office. Country Agreements
    - Agreements with Member Governments (Misc.) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement with and Concerning UNRRA (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement Ratifications (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Albania (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Mission Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Military Negotiations of Agreements during Military Period (Albania, Greece, Yugoslavia) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Australia (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement for Procurement of Supplies (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Contributions (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Red Cross (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Austria (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - DPs (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Freight Prepayment (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Pre-Draft (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Belgium (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - and France (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - and Luxembourg (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - and the Netherlands (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Bolivia, Agreement for Establishing amount of Contribution (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Brazil, Agreement for Procurement of Cotton Textiles (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement with Relative to Free Fund Purchases, Exchange Rate (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - "Decree Excempting UNRRA from Federal Tax" (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Meeting re Commodities (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Meeting re Commodities (Portuguese Text) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA Agreement (35) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Byelorussia Agreement, Byelo & English Texts (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Canada (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Contributions (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Casablanca Stockpile (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Chile (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Mixed Commission (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement re Procurement of Sodium Nitrate (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (44) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - China (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (English Text) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Railway Wagon Assembly (Kowloon Railway Co.) (Hong Kong) (293) (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Contracts (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Surplus Property Transfer (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement 201/1 (Box GC/14, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement #2 201/1 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Technical Training (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Colombia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement Pledging Administration and Operating Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Agreement (46) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Costa Rica (45) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Cuba (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Mixed Commission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Cuban Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Agreement (47) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Czechoslovakia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Seed Potatoes (96) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Sugar Contributed By Czechoslovakia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Bilateral Agreement with the Netherlands (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Claims Releases of (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Freight Pre-Payment (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Statement of Commodities (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Denmark Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Dodecanese (BMA) Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Dodecanese Agreement with UNRRA(152) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Dominican Republic (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Determining 2nd Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishing Mixed Commission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA Agreement (39) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Ecuador (205) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Egypt (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Ethiopia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Ethiopian Agreement (251) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Far East Mission Contributions (Syria & Lebanon) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Finland (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA & Finland (153) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Assistance Emergency Supply Program (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - France (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Bilateral Agreement with Belgium (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Contracts and Original Documents (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Czech. Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Luxembourg Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Netherlands Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Papers on Agreement between French Armies & UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Contracts with French Army (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Relations with French Government (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - French Indochina (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA French High Command Agreement (re DPs in Germany) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - French-Austria Military Governments Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greece (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Ability to Pay (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement Sale of Coal (82) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Freight Payment (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greek Mission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greek UN (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greece-UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UN Welfare Mission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - WHO (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greek Government (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Sale of Petrol Barrels (87) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greenland, Agreement with for 2,425,000 pounds of 1945 codfish involving (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Payment of $412,125.00 Food Division (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Greenland UNRRA Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Guatemala (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Haiti (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Haitian Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA and Haiti(48) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Honduras (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Honduran Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA And Honduras (50) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Hungary Emergency Assistance Relief (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Iceland (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement involving 3,340-Barrels of Codfish at a Cost of $57,114.00 Food Division (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement involving 1,450 Tons Codliver Oil at $582.60 per Ton -1,000 Ton at $650.00 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Procurement of 26,000 Barrels of Herring Involving $679,335.80: 25% Iceland Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - India (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Procurement of Supplies (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Iran (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Iraq (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Italy (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement(I) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (II) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Bais Document (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Lire Fund Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Medical Supply (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Supplementary Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - UNRRA-Italy Agreement (91) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Italian Mission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Italian Mission with Mennonite Control Commission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Korea, Agreement with UNRRA (155) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Liberia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Luxembourg (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Official Lease of Mess (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Mexico (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Mixed Commission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (41) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Memorandum of Agreement between UNRRA & NCCRS (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Netherlands (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Fisheries Board (6) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - And Czechoslovakia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Newfoundland (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement involving 3.8 millionpounds of Codifsh Dry Basis at a Cost of $745,000 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement re 23,000,000 pounds 1945 Codfish Production at a Cost of $4,250,000 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement f6r 100,000 Barrels of Herring (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for 200,000 barrels 1945/46 Herring Involving Payments of $3,200,000 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Fisheries Board, Herring (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - New Zealand (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Procurement of Supplies (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (32) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Nicaragua (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement July 1945, Procurement Coordination (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (49) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Norway (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Loan (272) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Panama (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishment of Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Paraguay (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with Establishment of Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (42) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Peru (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with Establishment of Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement for Establishing Mixed Commission (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (36) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Philippines (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (154) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Poland (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Freight Prepayment (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Surplus Property Disposal (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Portugal Contribution (233) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - Roumania Typhus Relief (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - San Marino (Box GC/15, Folder Side 1)
    - South Africa (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement for Procurement of Supplies (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (33) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - South America, Agreement with Documentation of Procurement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Southern Rhodesia, Agreement for Procurement of Supplies (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement with UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Sweden Contribution (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Swiss Contribution (241) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Swiss Silk Gauze (70) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Lire-Trieste (171) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Turkey Contribution(267) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Turkey Mission, Financial Consideration (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Ukraine SSR (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Ukraine Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UK (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Transfer of Army & Navy Surprop (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Polish Refugees (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - British European Airways Corp. (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Block Settlement Schedules (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Block Settlement (Ministry of Supply) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Bulk Settlement Final Agreement with Appendices 24 Mar. 1948 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Bulk Settlement, 24 Mar. 1948 (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UK/UNRRA Army Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UK/UNRRA/ERO financial Agreement Between Ministry of Supply & UNRRA I (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UK/UNRRA/ERO Financial Agreement Between Ministry~of Supply & UNRRA II (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - British Military (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Contributions (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UK/UNRRA C-in-C Boar & Military Governor of BZ in Germany (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Waiver Agreements & Schedules of Supplies to be Shipped by H MG (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - U.S.A. (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Tabulating Service US Agency Working Agreements with other Agencies and Bureau of Supply (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - US Public Health Service (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Interrelative Opinions (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - US Congress Joint Resolution to Enable US to Participate in the Work of UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Contributions (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Military Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Military Agreement UNRRA-USFA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - EUCOM (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - SACMED (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Treasure Procurement Contracts Transferred 30 June 1947 (428) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - USFET Agreement (183A) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA-USFET Relationship to CG USFET in US Zone Germany (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - UNRRA/Sheaf Agreement (011.9) (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Uruguay, Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Venezuela (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Yugoslavia (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Agreement (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
    - Freight Prepayment (Box GC/15, Folder Side 2)
  - Subseries VI.6: Insurance & Claims Division. Subject File